Student Association; Records ua804
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1943-1988; 6
  - Central Council: Student Tax Policy, Nomination Form, Correspondence and Flyers, ca. 1965 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Committee on Univ. Governance: SUNY Binghamton, Buffalo, Albany, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Committee Reports and Recommendations, 1950-1952 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Committee to Draft Campus Alcohol Policy - Recommendation, 1969 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Composition Services: styles and sizes, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Consolidated Laws and Regulations of SA, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Consolidated Laws and Regulations of SA, 1976 May 11 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Tentative Constitution of the State College Student Association, 1945 May 15 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Constitution, 1965 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Constitution, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Constitution, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Constitution SA Board, ca. 1962 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1951; 1959; 1970-1971 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Directories, 1970-1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Ebenezer Howard Project, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Elections: Flyers, 1972-1978; 1984-1987 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Financial Policies, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Financial Resolutions, 1943-1949 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Financial Statements, 1974 June 30 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Flyers and Brochures, ca. 1970-1986 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Forms, ca. 1965-1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Form Letters to Faculty Members, 1952; 1970; 1972; 1976; 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Form Letters to Students and Their Parents, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Government Reorganization Committee: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Government Revision Workshop, 1964 November (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Groups: Directory of student and other S.A. recognized groups, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Informer: Issues 1 and 2, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Living Area Affairs Commission: Rationale for women's hours, 1967 March 15 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Memorandum, 1968-1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Moving-up Day Programs and Recommendations, ca. 1940-1960 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - NYSCT Leadership Conference, 1954 March 23 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Off-Campus Student Co-op, 1975 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Operating Expenses: Central Council, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Press Release: Restoration of Carver Community Health Center Funding, 1973 October 5 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Procedures for Organizational Recognition, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Schedule for Letter Writing Campaign, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Student Affairs Council Minutes, 1974 February 5; 1974 March 6 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Student Association Handbook: SUNY Plattsburgh, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Student Evaluation of Courses and Teachers: Blank questionnaires and Instructions, ca. 1968-1974 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Student Government Conference: Information, Correspondence, Memoranda, 1964 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Student Government: Reorganization Workshop, 1964 November 21 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Student Senate: Government Reorganization Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Student Senate Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Student Senate: Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Transportation Committee: Rules and Regulations, Undated (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - University Athletics Council: Final Report, 1968 (Box 1 (6-Subject Files), Folder 63)
- Web Archives, 2006 August 30-2016 September 17; 7; 552 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - www.albany.edu/studentassociation/ - Internet Archive collection, 2006 August 30-2016 September 17 (Web-archive 2)